

SONI FAUZAN MAULANA

Purwakarta, Jawa Barat | 0897-1084-899 | sonifauzanm@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/sonifauzanm



SUMMARY

WhatsApp Contact

I am a 24 years old software engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in backend (API) and frontend (UI) software development life cycle. Good analytical and logical thinking, eagerness to learn, and good collaborative spirit.

WORK EXPERIENCE

CV. Infonet Global Tech

Bandung

Junior Software Engineer

Feb. 2020 - Feb. 2021

- Participate in the entire application lifecycle, focusing on coding and debugging.
- Build reusable code and libraries for future use.
- Doing test driven development.
- Develop, improve, and maintain high quality back-end services and APIs.
- Within a cross-functional team, collaborate with other developers specializing in backend, frontend, quality assurance, product owner, and scrum master.
- Apply design patterns and design principles to produce maintainable code.
- Learn multiple tech stacks to use the best tools for the job.
- Solve technical problems.
- Follow emerging technologies.

Lab. Teknik Informatika Universitas Gunadarma

Depok

Laboratory Assistant

Sep. 2018 - Sep. 2019

- Improve the practical manual (based on deficiencies in the previous and after years).
- Helping lecturers in carrying out practicum.
- Checking and assessing the practicum participant reports.
- Oversee the course of the practicum and is responsible for the smooth running of the practicum.
- Maintain equipment and cleanliness of the laboratory.

Mobile Apps Freelance

Depok

Internship at Washuh 98 Carwash

Sep. 2018

• Develop Point of Sales(POS) mobile apps.

In collaboration with DisHub. Kota Depok

Dec. 2018

• Develop reporting of traffic conditions mobile apps.

EDUCATION

Universitas Gunadarma

Depok

Bachelor of Engineering, Major in Informatics

Aug. 2015 - Aug. 2019

- GPA: 3,48 (Scale 4,00).
- Undergraduate thesis: Gender Classification on Face Images using CNN Method.
- Laboratory assistant.
- Scholarship recipients of YPKAAR PT. Adaro Indonesia.

SMA Negeri 1 Purwakarta

Purwakarta

Major in Science

2012 - 2015

- Student council member.
- Choir member.

LANGUANGE

• Bahasa Indonesia, English (passive).

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Programming (Java, C#, C++, Vue.JS, Flutter, XML, HTML, JavaScript, Dart, JSON, RestAPI, Python, GraphQL).
- Database (MySQL, SQL Server, PostgreSQL, Firebase, Oracle).
- Tools: Visual Studio Code, Android Studio, Git, NPM, Tortoise, Docker, Ms. Visual Studio, Postman, JIRA, Gitlab/Github, Google Colaboratory, Blender, Corel Draw, Figma, StarUML.

CERTIFICATIONS

Digital Talent Scholarship KOMINFO (Fresh Graduate Academy) Topic machine learning: Nov. 2019

- AWS cloud computing services.
- Python programming basics.
- Practice by using Pandas, NumPy, SciPy, MatplotLib libraries.
- Machine learning basics : regression, classification, and clustering.
- Deep learning models.
- TensorFlow, CNN, RNN, auto-encoder.

Indonesia Android Kejar Powered by Google	Jakarta
 Developing android apps for intermediate. 	Oct. 2016
• Developing android apps for beginner.	May, 2016
Lembaga Pengembangan Komputerisasi Universitas Gunadarma	Depok
Java programming language fundamental.	Jan. 2019
Oracle project.	Jan. 2019
• SQL server for intermediate.	Jul. 2018
Oracle for intermediate.	Jan. 2018
Networking fundamental.	Aug. 2016
• DBMS fundamental.	Jan. 2016